{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Storm \u0026 Hurricane Recovery Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"__cache./api/resource/task/40223/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40223,"taskName":"Recovery Service - Storm or Wind Damage","taskDescription":"Find a Storm or Wind Recovery Service","xmTaskDescriptor":"Storm \u0026 Hurricane Recovery Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":307,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Recovery Wind water hurricane Damage","textMessagingName":"Storm Damage Recvry","rolloverLongDesc":"Full service disaster recovery after floods including tornadoes, hurricanes, plumbing leaks or sewer backups. Typically familiar with insurance company policies \u0026 procedures.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes water removal, cleanup \u0026 repairs","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Find a Storm or Wind Recovery Service.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Storm Damage Recovery \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Hurricane \u0026 Wind Damage Recovery","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":63,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Storm or Wind Damage Recovery","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Recovery Service - Storm or Wind Damage","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Storm \u0026 Wind Recovery Service Need","urlName":"Recovery-Service-Storm-or-Wind-Damage","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Storm Damage Recovery Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Hurricane \u0026 Wind Damage","searchKeywords":"Recovery,Wind,water,hurricane,Damage,Storm","emcCategoryOid":-12022,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":530,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40223/":{"taskOID":40223,"originalTaskOID":40223,"setID":530,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4764,"questionDisplayText":"Damage Estimate","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How bad is the storm or wind damage?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7014,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Windows blown out","answerDisplayText":"Windows blown out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6851,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water damage in portion of house","answerDisplayText":"Water damage in portion of house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wind damage in portion of house","answerDisplayText":"Wind damage in portion of house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5397,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Roof damage","answerDisplayText":"Roof damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3461,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Landscape/yard damage","answerDisplayText":"Landscape/yard damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4762,"questionDisplayText":"When damage occurred","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"When did the damage occur?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3091,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Hours ago","answerDisplayText":"Hours ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6939,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Weeks ago","answerDisplayText":"Weeks ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3912,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Months ago","answerDisplayText":"Months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4753,"questionDisplayText":"Number of rooms affected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms are being affected?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":396,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-4","answerDisplayText":"2-4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":516,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5-10","answerDisplayText":"5-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2237,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entire house","answerDisplayText":"Entire house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4763,"questionDisplayText":"Structure Problems","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What part of the interior structure is affected? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1305,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ceilings","answerDisplayText":"Ceilings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2549,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floors","answerDisplayText":"Floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4764,"questionDisplayText":"Damage Estimate","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How bad is the storm or wind damage?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7014,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Windows blown out","answerDisplayText":"Windows blown out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6851,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water damage in portion of house","answerDisplayText":"Water damage in portion of house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wind damage in portion of house","answerDisplayText":"Wind damage in portion of house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5397,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Roof damage","answerDisplayText":"Roof damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3461,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Landscape/yard damage","answerDisplayText":"Landscape/yard damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7014,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Windows blown out","answerDisplayText":"Windows blown out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6851,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water damage in portion of house","answerDisplayText":"Water damage in portion of house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wind damage in portion of house","answerDisplayText":"Wind damage in portion of house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5397,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Roof damage","answerDisplayText":"Roof damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3461,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Landscape/yard damage","answerDisplayText":"Landscape/yard damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4762,"questionDisplayText":"When damage occurred","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"When did the damage occur?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3091,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Hours ago","answerDisplayText":"Hours ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6939,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Weeks ago","answerDisplayText":"Weeks ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3912,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Months ago","answerDisplayText":"Months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3091,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Hours ago","answerDisplayText":"Hours ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6939,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Weeks ago","answerDisplayText":"Weeks ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3912,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Months ago","answerDisplayText":"Months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4753,"questionDisplayText":"Number of rooms affected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms are being affected?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":396,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-4","answerDisplayText":"2-4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":516,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5-10","answerDisplayText":"5-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2237,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entire house","answerDisplayText":"Entire house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":396,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-4","answerDisplayText":"2-4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":516,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5-10","answerDisplayText":"5-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2237,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entire house","answerDisplayText":"Entire house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4763,"questionDisplayText":"Structure Problems","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What part of the interior structure is affected? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1305,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ceilings","answerDisplayText":"Ceilings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2549,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floors","answerDisplayText":"Floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1305,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ceilings","answerDisplayText":"Ceilings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2549,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floors","answerDisplayText":"Floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}